It's just surprising to me
that you can't swim, Bell.
I never had a reason to swim
in the other world.
'Cause I could do this.
Magic?!
You aren't allowed to use magic!
Seriously? But it makes things easier.
You'll attract attention! Get down here!
Eek, Hinata! Catch me!
Huh? Wait—
Oh! Hinata, you dog.
B-Bell! Fix your swimsuit!
Sunohara?!
I'm sorry.
You're such a pain, I swear...
Magic is off limits for today.
Bell!
With one of these,
it doesn't even matter if you can swim!
You'll have just as much fun
using a floatie instead of magic!
Sakura...!
Thanks.
Hey, look!
It's a dolphin!
How cute!
Look at the camera! Say cheese!
Bell!
Sunohara! Bell!
Are you okay?
Uh-huh. I've got my life jacket.
I'm glad you weren't hurt.
Y'know, since you can't swim.
Hinata...
You're always coming to my rescue.
You really are my hero, Hinata!
B-Bell? C'mon, you're way too close—
Oh please, this is nothing.
If you and I were to—
Are you two okay?!
Hey, you guys! Now that Bell's
gotten used to the ocean...
wanna have another race?
Huh? But...
I'll be fine!
Besides, I want to see you look cool
out there in the water.
Ready...
Go!
Cecil takes the lead!
Hinata's right on her tail!
Don't stop! Keep it up!
You alright?
Racing with a floatie kinda sucks...
The dolphin we saw earlier?
I'd expect nothing less, Lord Hinata!
But I won't lose!
Neither will I!
So fast!
First place!
Wow, what an upset!
The winner is Bell!
A dolphin?!
That's not fair!
Direct all your complaints to the dolphin.
Talk about raining on our parade...
Are you okay, Cecil?
Damn fish...
He's a naughty little rascal, isn't he?
Sure is.
He stole Lady Sakura's swimsuit!
Seems like he just wants to play.
Give it back!
I'll handle this.
B-Bell?!
We've got to get Sakura's swimsuit back!
Hey.
What? You're seriously gonna tell me
not to use my magic?
On the contrary. Cast it on us, too.
Our target is the dolphin!
Our objective is securing the swimsuit!
Oh, this brings back memories!
Now let's get moving!
Water spirits, lend me your power!
Sorry, didn't mean to scare you.
But my friend really needs that back.
Success!
Excellent job, Lord Hinata!
Um, can you not wave it around like that?
It's already getting late.
Maybe we oughtta pack it in.
I got some great footage.
Can't wait to edit it!
Hinata, let's go explore over there!
Ah, wait a minute, Bell!
Sunohara!
I'm going to head home, too.
Huh? In that case, we'll go with—
Isn't there something
you need to talk to Bell about?
Y'see, I... came to a realization recently.
You two are always so cheerful and caring,
and it makes me happy.
So...
...good luck!
Yeah. Thanks.
God, I'm an idiot.
What is this thing?
A piece of coral.
It must've washed up here.
May would say we should
put it "on the 'gram."
So, you're learning internet slang, too.
Of course.
I pick it up from being around you.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, it is.
Hinata, to be honest...
Before I came here, all I could
think about was seeing you again.
You're still my number one priority,
that hasn't changed. But...
I've seen so many new things, and...
The world you call home,
I've come to appreciate
what type of place it is.
Which is why...
while I love you very much,
I also love this world!
I'm glad I came here!
Me, too. I'm glad you
came to my world— no.
I'm glad I met you, Bell.
Bell!
Yeah?
I love you, too!
I don't want to lose you!
I want to be with you forever!
A-Although, it might be tough
since I'm a human
and elves live for such a long time...
but I'll try my hardest to
make sure you won't be sad—
Hinata!
Y-Yeah?
Wh-Wh-What you said just now...
can you say it one more time?
Of course.
I love you, Bell.
Hi-na-ta!
Bell, you're way too close.
Aw, where's the harm? Is it a problem?
No, I guess it's not a big deal...
G'morning, Sunohara. G'morning, Bell.
Sakura!
Good morning, Mochida.
The video's done!
Summer Memories
What a great meal!
Your cooking is delicious
as always, Hinata.
Thanks.
Well, I'll go ahead and clean up—
Hi-na-ta!
What's wrong?
I wouldn't mind having dessert, too.
Dessert?
I think we have some custard in the fridge—
Jeez... That's not what I meant.
I want you for dessert.
There's no reason to
hold back anymore, is there?
Y-Yeah...
But can you wait? Let me shower before—
Nope, no way!
Ever since this morning— no.
I've been waiting patiently all this time!
Hey, Hinata...
How many kids do you want?
K-Kids?!
It's a little early to start thinking
about things like that...
Don't be naïve!
You're constantly surrounded by
a whole bunch of women as it is!
Bell...
Don't worry. I can't even imagine myself
with anyone except for you.
Bell?
That settles it...
I already made my decision,
but this drives it home!
Hinata!
Bell?! You've got that really crazy
look in your eyes!
It's your fault, y'know.
I lose all sense of reason because of you.
Wait—!
We should have at least three kids, right?
I don't mind whether they're boys or girls,
but I would like at least one girl!
Oh, and we'll have to find a place to live!
This apartment is a little too small.
Ideally, we'd have a dog or other pets,
and we'd be surrounded by family too, of course.
Then, on holidays,
we'll all go fishing as a family,
Sh-She's intense...
and at night, we'll sit down together
and eat a nice dinner...
Hinata...
A female dark elf named Mariabell.
I met her in another world, and...
she's slightly obsessed with me...
I love you, Hinata!
I love you too, Bell.
But she's a very pure-hearted girl,
and very cute.
Now then...
It's time for dessert!